Guide to the Stanford University, Department of Special Collections and University Archives, Catalogs
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Department of Special Collections and University Archives, catalogs
1927-2004
SC4-6270-5
Stanford University. Libraries. Department of Special Collections and University Archives.
0.5 Linear feet
Archival copies of catalogs and microfilm guides for collections held by the Department of Special Collections.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Description of the Collection
Archival copies of catalogs and microfilm guides for collections held by the Department of Special Collections.
Description of the Collection
Archival copies of catalogs and microfilm guides for collections held by the Department of Special Collections.
Access Terms
Stanford University. Libraries. Department of Special Collections and University Archives.; Library catalogs.
Collection Contents
- Catalogs
  - Printing in Greenland with A List of Greenland Imprints in the Krabbe Library, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Finely Printed Books Presented to the Library of Stanford University: A Catalogue, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The William R. Shafter Papers, 1862-1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Finely Printed Books Presented to the Library of Stanford University: A Catalogue, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Census of Aldines in California, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Francis B. Loomis Papers, 1835-1959 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Francis B. Loomis Papers, 1835-1959 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Research Guide to the Records of MALDEF / PRLDEF, 1968-1983, 1972-1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - A Catalogue of the John Steinbeck Collection at Stanford University, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - The Barchas Collection at Stanford University, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - A Vast and Useful Art, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Portraits A Catalog of Prints in the Stanford University Library, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Incunabula, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 13)